JIHEE MOON

QLD 4215 0423692155 mj824m@gmail.com github.com/jiheemoon linkedin.com/in/jihee-moon-450737178

Professional Summary

Analytical Java Developer with 3+ years of experience handling popular web languages and Javascript to develop and implement applications based on customers' needs. Exceptional technical skills in coding and software development. Forward-thinking professional talented at developing creative solutions for complex technical problems.

Work History

Java Developer APR 2019 - MAY 2022

HAESOLDATA Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul, Korea

Collaborated in a team-based, Agile environment to accomplish objectives by deadlines. Participated in requirements gathering and design development meetings. Reviewed code and debugged errors to improve performance. Wrote, modified and maintained software documentation and specifications.

E-learning system Maintenance FEB 2021 - FEB 2022

Development and Establishment of CRM MAY 2020 - JAN 2021

Development of AD Connector (SSO) APR 2020 - MAY 2020

Development and Establishment of Internal Accounting System APR 2019 - APR 2020

Education

Academy in Java Framework DeveloperTraining Course OCT 2018 - MAR 2019

KH Information Education Center, Seoul, Korea

Bachelor of Science: Smart IT MAR 2015 - FEB 2019

Doowon Technical University Paju, Gyeonggi Province, Korea

Skills

Linux Environments Spring DAO Software Deployment JavaScript

Web Programming Security Planning

Critical Thinking RDMS Development and SQL

Spring MVC

Apache Maven

User Interface (UI)

SOAP and Restful Web Services

Organization and Time Management

Performance Evaluation and Optimization

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

Source and Version Control: Git, GitHub

Apache Tomcat Programming Languages: Java, Python

Accomplishments

Anti freezing system using ac current

source link: https://github.com/jiheemoon/DonPaBangz

Certifications

Industrial Engineer Information Processing Human Resources Development Service of Korea	MAR 2019
Linux Master Grade II KAIT	DEC 2018
International Manual Driver License	FEB 2015
Additional Information	
Working holiday VISA - unrestricted working rights	JUL 2023
Doowon Philine Language training - GITC School	JAN 2018
Kintex science creative festival - An explanation of the fusion of Arduino and art	AUG 2017
Canada Working holiday	JUL 2016

Volunteer Experience

Doowon Rose 10th Vietnam Volunteer JUN 2016